Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Periodicals and Publications, 1955-2007
  - Small Press Publications, 1955-2006
    - Dwight York and the Nuwaubian Nation, 1992-2001
      - Tents of Kedar/Nubian Islamic Hebrews, Undated (Box 493, Folder 1)
        Ed. 3, 21, 27, 64, 76
      - Tents of Kedar/Nubian Islamic Hebrews, Undated (Box 493, Folder 2)
        Ed. 121, 148, 152
      - Tents of Kedar/Nubian Islamic Hebrews, Undated (Box 493, Folder 3)
        Ed. 198
      - Tents of Kedar/Nubian Islamic Hebrews, Undated (Box 493, Folder 4)
        Ed. 104, 110, 132, 140
      - Tents of Kedar/Nubian Islamic Hebrews, Undated (Box 494, Folder 1)
        Ed. 141, 158, 171, 177, 197
      - Holy Tabernacle Mysteries, Undated (Box 494, Folder 2)
        Scroll Nos. 22, 34, 45, 54, 91, 92, 93, 97, 99, 107, 122, 123, 163, 165, 171, 188
      - Holy Tabernacle Mysteries, Undated (Box 495, Folder 1)
        Ed. 10-18
      - Holy Tabernacle Mysteries, Undated (Box 495, Folder 2)
        Ed. 1-2, Scroll No. 17
      - Holy Tabernacle Mysteries, Undated (Box 495, Folder 3)
        Scroll Nos. 47-48
      - Holy Tabernacle Mysteries, Undated (Box 495, Folder 4)
        Scroll Nos. 80-81
      - Holy Tabernacle Mysteries, Undated (Box 495, Folder 5)
        Scroll Nos. 82, 94, 101
      - Holy Tabernacle Mysteries, Undated (Box 495, Folder 6)
        Scroll Nos. 130-131
      - Holy Tabernacle Mysteries, Undated (Box 496, Folder 1)
        Scroll Nos. 133, 134, 140
      - Holy Tabernacle Mysteries, Undated (Box 496, Folder 2)
        Scroll No. 140
      - Holy Tabernacle Mysteries, Undated (Box 496, Folder 3)
      - Holy Tabernacle Mysteries, Undated (Box 496, Folder 4)
      - Holy Tabernacle Mysteries, Undated (Box 496, Folder 5)
        Scroll Nos. 140, 142
      - Holy Tabernacle Mysteries, Undated (Box 496, Folder 6)
        Scroll Nos. 143-144
      - Holy Tabernacle Mysteries, Undated (Box 497, Folder 1)
        Scroll No. 156
      - Holy Tabernacle Mysteries, Undated (Box 497, Folder 2)
        Scroll Nos. 147, 162
      - Holy Tabernacle Mysteries, Undated (Box 497, Folder 3)
        Scroll Nos. 190-191
      - Holy Tabernacle Mysteries, Undated (Box 497, Folder 4)
        Scroll Nos. 192, 198
      - Holy Tabernacle Mysteries, Undated (Box 497, Folder 5)
        Scroll No. 360
      - Holy Tabernacle Mysteries, Undated (Box 497, Folder 6)
        Revised Edition Scroll No. 15
      - Holy Tabernacle Mysteries, Undated (Box 498, Folder 1)
        The Millenium Book Part 1
      - Holy Tabernacle Mysteries, Undated (Box 498, Folder 2)
        The Millenium Book Part 2
      - Holy Tabernacle Mysteries, Undated (Box 498, Folder 3)
    - Surveillance, Technology, Survivalist, and Safety, 1984-2005
      - 1984 and "1984": Where and How Have George Orwell's Forecasts Come True?, 1984; Sturua, Melor (Box 480, Folder 6)
      - Bodyguarding: A Complete Manual, 1995 (Box 477, Folder 4)
      - The Computerized Afrikan and Other Techno-Woes, 1997; Kupendua, Jahfree I.; Beebe, Barbara (Box 477, Folder 5)
      - Detective Store International, Undated (Box 477, Folder 6)
      - Identity, Privacy, and Personal Freedom: Big Brother vs. The New Resistance, 1999; Charrett, Sheldon (Box 477, Folder 7)
      - National Homeland Security Agency - "Out of Evil comes a Great Good", 2005 (Box 477, Folder 8)
      - Recent Implant Technologies, 1992 (Box 477, Folder 9)
      - Schwarzman Export Import Co., Undated (Box 480, Folder 1)
        Catalog 13
      - Street Gangs: The Law Enforcement Guide to Today's Urban Violence, 1995 (Box 480, Folder 2)
      - Surveillance Cameras in Harlem, 2002 (Box 480, Folder 3)
      - What Should You Do If You Are Arrested or Framed by the Police or FBI?, 1990; Muhammad, Al-Hajj Idris A. (Box 480, Folder 4)
      - Y2K Citizen's Action Guide, 1998 (Box 480, Folder 5)
  - Periodicals, 1980-2007
    - Hip Hop, Music, and Art, 1980-2007
      - 11211, 2004 (Box 505, Folder 6)
        Volume 5, number 1
      - Aelle, 1995 (Box 502, Folder 1)
      - Apeman, 1998 (Box 502, Folder 2)
      - Awake!, 2001-05-08 (Box 502, Folder 3)
      - Big Daddy, Undated (Box 502, Folder 4)
        Issue 8
      - Blues & Soul, 1987 (Box 491, Folder 8)
      - Bounce, 1999-09 (Box 502, Folder 5)
      - Ca Plane, 1981-05 (Box 502, Folder 6)
        Volume 1
      - Capoeira, Undated (Box 502, Folder 7)
        Year 1, numbers 3 & 5; Year 2, numbers 9 & 12
      - Centro de Estudios Puertorriqueños, 1990-1993 (Box 502, Folder 8)
      - Centro de Estudios Puertorriqueños, 1992-1997 (Box 502, Folder 9)
      - Centro de Estudios Puertorriqueños Bulletin, 1991-1992 (Box 505, Folder 7)
      - Chart-Beat Magazine, 1985-07 (Box 503, Folder 1)
      - Clark Magazine, 2001 (Box 503, Folder 2)
      - CMJ Music Marathon Update, 1990 (Box 505, Folder 8)
      - CMJ Music Marathon, 1990-10-24-1990-10-27 (Box 505, Folder 9)
      - Comité Noviembre, 1992 (Box 505, Folder 10)
      - Comité Noviembre, 1996 (Box 503, Folder 3)
      - Coup D'État, 2005-10 (Box 503, Folder 4)
      - Dance Xpress, 1989-04 (Box 503, Folder 5)
        Number 4
      - Details, 1998-11 (Box 503, Folder 6)
      - DMR: House Music Report, 1990 (Box 503, Folder 8)
        Volume 13 issue 20
      - Doula: The Volume of Rap Music and Hip Hop Culture, 2001 (Box 503, Folder 7)
        Volume 1 issue 2
      - Elemental Magazine, Undated (Box 503, Folder 9)
        Volume 4 Issue 42
      - Enlace Funk, 2001 (Box 503, Folder 10)
      - Full Disclosure, 1996 (Box 503, Folder 11)
        Volume I, number 5
      - Future Style, 1992 (Box 491, Folder 9)
      - Game Informer, 2005 (Box 491, Folder 10)
        Issue 146
      - H2O: Hip-Hop Film Festival, 2002 (Box 503, Folder 12)
      - Hip Hop Connection, 1991-01 (Box 491, Folder 11)
        Number 24
      - Hip-Hop Connection, 1996-10 (Box 505, Folder 11)
      - Holland Rocks - Dutch Rock Music Foundation, 1990-07 (Box 505, Folder 12)
        Update 3
      - The Hype Mag, 1997 (Box 503, Folder 13)
      - Icon, 1998-10 (Box 503, Folder 14)
      - JET, 1980-12-25 (Box 505, Folder 13)
      - JOR Quarterly, 1992 (Box 503, Folder 15)
        Volume 2 number 3
      - Juice, 2000-2002 (Box 503, Folder 16)
      - Kaze Magazine, Undated (Box 503, Folder 17)
        Issue 10
      - L'Affiche, Undated (Box 503, Folder 18)
        Number 95
      - Le Matin Deparis, 1984 (Box 491, Folder 12)
      - Life, 1990 (Box 503, Folder 19)
      - Loud, 1999-09 (Box 503, Folder 20)
        Number 59
      - Mad: DJ Series, 1997 (Box 503, Folder 21)
      - Mixer, 1999-2000 (Box 503, Folder 22)
      - Mixmag, 1994 (Box 504, Folder 1)
        Volume 2 Issue number 43
      - Music Magazine, 1999-09 (Box 505, Folder 3)
      - The Musician's Atlas, 2001 (Box 504, Folder 2)
      - The Musician's Guide to Touring, 2001 (Box 504, Folder 3)
      - New York Review of Records (NYROR), 1990 (Box 505, Folder 14)
        Volume 1, number 4
      - Ozone Magazine, 2007 (Box 505, Folder 4)
      - PLUR, 1997 (Box 504, Folder 4)
      - PM, 2004-10 (Box 504, Folder 5)
      - Re:Up Manual 006, 2005 (Box 504, Folder 8)
      - Red Eye, 2001-05 (Box 504, Folder 6)
      - Reflex, 1990 (Box 505, Folder 15)
        Volume 2, issue 2
      - Reggae Report, 1990 (Box 505, Folder 16)
        Volume 8, number 1
      - Retailer's Buying Guide, 1994 (Box 504, Folder 7)
      - Rockpool, 1987-04-24 (Box 505, Folder 17)
        Volume 7, issue 7
      - Rockstar, 1988 (Box 491, Folder 13)
        Number 94
      - Seconds, 1995 (Box 504, Folder 9)
      - Slap, 1996-05 (Box 491, Folder 14)
      - Soul Underground, 1990-03 (Box 491, Folder 17)
      - Soul Underground, 1990-03 (Box 504, Folder 14)
        Issue 29
      - The Source, 1990 (Box 491, Folder 15)
        Volume 3 number 1
      - The Source, 1990-03-2005 (Box 505, Folder 18)
      - The Source, 2002 (Box 504, Folder 10)
        Number 150
      - Sphinx, 1991-09 (Box 491, Folder 16)
      - Streetsound, 1995-08 (Box 504, Folder 12)
        Number 79
      - Stress, 1998 (Box 504, Folder 11)
        Issue 13
      - The Sunday Times, Undated (Box 505, Folder 5)
      - Terminal Zone, Undated (Box 505, Folder 19)
      - Touch, 1991-10 (Box 505, Folder 20)
      - Twenty4seven, 2001-03 (Box 504, Folder 13)
      - Urb, 1990-2004 (Box 504, Folder 16)
      - Urban Sound, 1995 (Box 504, Folder 15)
      - XXL, 2006-03 (Box 505, Folder 1)
        Number 78
      - Zulu Nation Poland, Undated (Box 505, Folder 2)
    - Science, Technology, and History, 1989-2006
      - 21st Century Science & Technology, 2003 (Box 489, Folder 8)
      - American Legacy, 2000-2002 (Box 489, Folder 9)
        Volumes 6.3, 8.3
      - Ancient American: Archaeology of the Americas Before Columbus, 2004 (Box 489, Folder 10)
        Volume 9, number 55
      - Astronomy, 1996-2000 (Box 489, Folder 11)
      - Astronomy & Space, 1997-06 (Box 489, Folder 12)
        Volume 4, number 5
      - Discover, 2002-03 (Box 490, Folder 1)
        Volume 23, number 3
      - Discover, 2006-02 (Box 505, Folder 22)
      - Fortune, 2003 (Box 505, Folder 23)
        Volume 147, number 5
      - Frontiers, 1989-12 (Box 490, Folder 2)
      - Kiplinger's Personal Finance, 2006-02 (Box 490, Folder 4)
      - KMT: A Modern Journal of Ancient Egypt, 2004 (Box 490, Folder 3)
        Volumes 14.1, 15.1
      - Military History, 1996-06 (Box 490, Folder 5)
      - National Geographic: exploring space, 2004 (Box 490, Folder 6)
      - National Museum of the American Indian, 2001 (Box 490, Folder 7)
      - New Life, 1999 (Box 490, Folder 8)
      - New Scientist, 1999-09 (Box 490, Folder 9)
      - Newsweek, 1998-1999 (Box 490, Folder 10)
      - Odyssey, 2002 (Box 490, Folder 11)
      - PC Magazine, 2001 (Box 490, Folder 12)
      - Popular Mechanics, 2000-2006 (Box 490, Folder 13)
      - Popular Science, 2000-2004 (Box 490, Folder 14)
      - Scientific American, 1999-2004 (Box 490, Folder 15)
      - Sky News, 1999 (Box 490, Folder 16)
      - Spectrum, 1999 (Box 490, Folder 17)
        Issue 67
      - T'ai Chi, 1999 (Box 491, Folder 1)
        Volume 23 number 4
      - TIME, 1997-08 (Box 491, Folder 2)
      - To Your Health, 1999 (Box 491, Folder 3)
      - U.S. News & World Report, 1999 (Box 491, Folder 4)
      - Web Bound, 2001 (Box 491, Folder 6)
        Volume 6 issue 2
      - Windows Tips, 2001 (Box 491, Folder 7)
        Volume 7 issue 5
      - The Web: PC How-To Guide, 2001 (Box 491, Folder 5)
    - UFO and Paranormal
      - AA&ES, 2004 (Box 487, Folder 1)
      - Alien Encounters, 1996-1997 (Box 487, Folder 2)
        Issues 6, 7, 9, 10, 14
      - Alternate Perceptions: Journal of UFOs, History, Native Spirituality & Paranormal Phenomenon, 1996-1997 (Box 487, Folder 3)
        Issue 52
      - Atlantis Rising, 2001-2003 (Box 487, Folder 4)
        Issues 19, 30, 40
      - Astronomy, 2000-07 (Box 487, Folder 5)
      - Bizarre, 1997-05-1997-06 (Box 487, Folder 6)
      - Borderlands: A Quarterly Journal of Borderland Research, 1997 (Box 487, Folder 7)
        Volume 53, Number 2
      - Catalyst, 1996-11-1996-12 (Box 487, Folder 8)
        Issue 3
      - The Ecologist, 2001-03 (Box 487, Folder 9)
        Volume 31, Number 2
      - Uri Geller's Encounters, 1997 (Box 487, Folder 10)
        Issues 3, 4, 6, 11
      - Enigma, 1996-1997 (Box 487, Folder 11)
        Issue 4
      - Eagle Wings International, 1996 (Box 487, Folder 12)
        Volume 5, Number 1
      - Fangoria, 2002-09-2004-05 (Box 487, Folder 13)
        Numbers 216, 232
      - FATE, 1997-03 (Box 505, Folder 21)
      - Fortean Times - Folder 1, 1996-1997 (Box 487, Folder 14)
        Numbers 83, 94, 96, 99
      - Fortean Times - Folder 2, 1998-2004 (Box 488, Folder 1)
        Numbers 109, 117, 126, 155, 161, 162, 182
      - Independence Day, 1996 (Box 488, Folder 2)
      - NEXUS, 1997-2004 (Box 488, Folder 3)
        Volumes 4.1, 4.4, 6.5, 9.3, 11.2
      - Paranoia, 2001 (Box 488, Folder 4)
        Issue 26
      - A Complete Guide to Paranormal Phenomenon, 1996 (Box 488, Folder 5)
      - Sightings, Undated (Box 488, Folder 6)
      - Skeptics, 1996 (Box 488, Folder 7)
      - Skeptical Inquirer, 1997-2001 (Box 488, Folder 8)
        Volumes 21.4, 25.2
      - UFO: The Journal of UFO Investigations, Undated (Box 488, Folder 9)
        Volume 10
      - UFO: The Science & Phenomena Magazine, 2001-2003 (Box 488, Folder 10)
        Volumes 16.2, 16.5, 17.1, 17.4, 18.1, 18.3
      - UFO Magazine, 1996-1997 (Box 488, Folder 11)
      - UFO Magazine, 1998-2004 (Box 489, Folder 1)
      - UFO Reality, 1996-1997 (Box 489, Folder 2)
        Issues 5, 6, 7
      - UFO Sightings, 1997 (Box 489, Folder 3)
        Volume 5, number 2
      - UFO Times, 1997 (Box 489, Folder 4)
        Issue 45
      - UFO Universe, 1996-1997 (Box 489, Folder 5)
      - The Unopened Files, 1996-1997 (Box 489, Folder 6)
      - The X-Factor, 1996 (Box 489, Folder 7)
  - Other Publications, 1971-1996
    - Amnesty International, 1988 (Box 549, Folder 5)
    - Black Feeling Black Talk, 1972; Broadside Press; Giovanni, Nikki (Box 546, Folder 4)
      Third edition, second printing.
    - Calypso Carnival Pageant, 1971 (Box 545, Folder 8)
    - Concert Program: The New Birth, The Funkadelics, The Natural Four, New York City and WWRl's, Gerry B. at the Apollo, 1972 (Box 545, Folder 7)
    - Eagle Bird One, 1996; Hinton, Charles (Box 548, Folder 8)
    - Favourite Sierra Leone Recipes, 1978; Greene, Pamela (Box 546, Folder 5)
    - Hot Summer Rock with Mandrill, Buddy Miles, Bloodstone, Rare Earth, Osibisa, Funkadelic, 1973; Powell, Teddy (Box 546, Folder 7)
    - Superstars, 1974 (Box 546, Folder 6)
    - Technics SL-2000 instructions, 1977; Panasonic Company (Box 546, Folder 3)
    - The World Famous Apollo Theatre Stars, 1973 (Box 545, Folder 9)
  - Publications from 3410 De Reimer Ave. Bronx, NY, 1961-1985
    - Music
      - Festival! The Book of American Celebrations, 1970; Marshall, Jim; Wolman, Baron; Hopkins, Jerry (Box 480, Folder 11)
      - Future Pop: Music for the Eighties, 1983; Noble, Peter L. (Box 480, Folder 7)
      - The Harmony Illustrated Encyclopedia of Rock, 1982; Bonds, Ray (Box 482, Folder 1)
      - Le Choc Michael Jackson, 1985; Abitan, Guy; Abitan, Danièle (Box 480, Folder 10)
      - Papa Joe's Boys: The Jacksons Story, 1983 (Box 480, Folder 8)
      - Right On! Poster Book, 1983 (Box 480, Folder 9)
    - Ansaru Allah Community
      - Back to the Beginning: The Book of Names, 1979; Ansaru Allah Community (Box 482, Folder 2)
      - Christianity: The Political Religion, Undated; Ansaru Allah Community (Box 482, Folder 8)
      - Contradictions of the Disciples, 1981; Ansaru Allah Community (Box 482, Folder 17)
      - Did the Hog Come For Mankind?, Undated; Ansaru Allah Community (Box 482, Folder 14)
      - The Dog, Undated; Ansaru Allah Community (Box 482, Folder 19)
      - The Fallacy of Easter, 1980; Ansaru Allah Community (Box 482, Folder 3)
      - Fast of Ramadan, 1979; Ansaru Allah Community (Box 482, Folder 10)
      - The Forgotten Tribe Kedar, Undated; Ansaru Allah Community (Box 482, Folder 21)
      - From Allah to Man, 1977; Ansaru Allah Community (Box 482, Folder 13)
      - Hadith: Allah's Scriptures Comes First!, Ansaru Allah Community (Box 482, Folder 20)
      - Khutbat's of Al Hajj Al Imam Isa Abd'Allah Muhammad Al Mahdi, 1974; Ansaru Allah Community (Box 482, Folder 7)
      - The Message of the Messenger is Right and Exact, Undated; Ansaru Allah Community (Box 482, Folder 16)
      - Muslim Prayer Book, Undated; Ansaru Allah Community (Box 482, Folder 18)
      - Our Last Flag: By "Our" I Mean All Ex-Slaves, Undated; Ansaru Allah Community (Box 482, Folder 15)
      - The Pale Man, 1977; Ansaru Allah Community (Box 482, Folder 9)
      - The Tribe Israel is No More!, Undated; Ansaru Allah Community (Box 482, Folder 6)
      - The True Story of the Prophet Abraham (Pbuh), Undated; Ansaru Allah Community (Box 482, Folder 12)
      - What is a Masjid?, 1977; Ansaru Allah Community (Box 482, Folder 4)
      - Who Was Noble Drew Ali?, 1980; Ansaru Allah Community (Box 482, Folder 5)
      - Why Allah Should Not Be Called "God", Undated; Ansaru Allah Community (Box 482, Folder 11)
    - Religion
      - Al-Ittihad, Undated (Box 486, Folder 5)
      - Back to Godhead: The Magazine of the Hare Krishna Movement, Undated (Box 486, Folder 6)
      - Books & Things: Specializing in Islamic Literature, Undated (Box 486, Folder 3)
      - The Muslim Prayer Book, 1974; Ali, Maulana Muhammad (Box 486, Folder 1)
      - My Arabic Alphabet Book, 1963; Naeem, Andul Basit (Box 486, Folder 4)
      - The Woman in Islam Educational Series, 1981 (Box 486, Folder 2)
    - Black Power, Achievement, Thought
      - A Glorious Age in Africa, 1965; Chu, Daniel; Skinner, Elliot (Box 482, Folder 24)
      - A Crowell Biography: Malcom X, 1970; Adoff, Arnold (Box 486, Folder 11)
      - Nigeria Fact Sheet: Industrial Development, Undated (Box 486, Folder 10)
      - Sud-Ouest ivoirien, Undated (Box 486, Folder 13)
      - The Journal of Negro History, 1974; Williams, Lorraine A. (Box 486, Folder 12)
      - The Quotable Karenga, 1967 (Box 486, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous
      - 700 Years Amsterdam - 700 good reasons to go there!, 1975 (Box 486, Folder 18)
      - Come to the UN pamphlet, Undated (Box 486, Folder 17)
      - Ghent - Belgium, Undated (Box 486, Folder 20)
      - Guide to Federal Consumer Service, 1976 (Box 486, Folder 16)
      - Macy's catalog, Undated (Box 486, Folder 22)
      - Mossberg, 1977 (Box 486, Folder 14)
      - The Metropolitan Museum of Art Guide to the Collections: Egyptian Art, 1973 (Box 486, Folder 15)
      - Trinity Episcopal Church Financial Report, 1995 (Box 486, Folder 21)
      - Windmills in Holland, 1970 (Box 486, Folder 19)
      - The American Civil War, 1961; Aptheker, Herbert (Box 482, Folder 23)
      - What Made the U.S. Great, 1968 (Box 482, Folder 22)
      - Black is the Color, 1975-05; Brown, Kathy (Box 486, Folder 8)
      - How to Study in College, 1962; Pauk, Walter (Box 486, Folder 7)
- Ephemera, 1983-2013
  - Promo photos - Other artists, 1985-2000 (Box 548, Folder 1)
  - Operation Graffiti Works, 1994 (Box 548, Folder 7)
  - Dark Shadows, 1995 (Box 549, Folder 1)
  - Kublai K.M. Toure - Jefferson Awards, 1998 (Box 548, Folder 5)
  - Travel ephemera, 1998 (Box 549, Folder 4)
  - Comic books, 1999-2002 (Box 549, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous prints, 2000 (Box 548, Folder 2)
    Commercial prints and print outs of Louis Farrakhan, the Nuwaubian Nation, and other religious figures.
  - Music industry and music catalogs and advertisements, 1983-1991 (Box 546, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous flyers and promo, other artists, 1985-2000 (Box 546, Folder 15)
  - Stickers and promo, other artists, 1985-2000 (Box 546, Folder 17)
  - Press kits and press releases, other artists, 1993-2001 (Box 546, Folder 14)
  - Million Man March calendar, 1996 (Box 546, Folder 19)
  - Justice By Uniting in Creative Energy Replication Manual, 2005; J.U.i.C.E. (Box 532)
  - The Afrika Bambaataa Master of Records Open Archive, 2013-07-2013-08 (Box 548, Folder 3)
    Press release and guest book.
  - Crossword puzzles, Undated (Box 549, Folder 6)
  - Menus, Undated (Box 549, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 549, Folder 8)
    Contains miscellaneous web print outs and clippings.
  - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 549, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous religious pamphlets and ephemera, Undated (Box 549, Folder 10)
    Includes pamphlets from the Nuwaubian Nation.
  - Notes, Undated (Box 549, Folder 11)
    Contains miscellaneous handwritten notes.